Finding Aid for the Paul Friedländer Papers, 1848-1976 LSC.1551
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Offprints and pamphlets from the Friedländer library
  - Wrede, Walther, "Attika" (Vortrag in der Deutschen Arbeitsgemeinschaft zu Athen) Athens: Deutsches Archäologisches Institut,., 1934; 2462.; Text + pls. 1-23 (Inscribed). (Box 46)
  - Wrede, W. "Der Maskengott" Athenische Mitteilungen 53,., 1928; 2463.; pp.66-95, Beil. XXVII-XXVIII, Taf.1-4 (Offprint, inscribed). (Box 46)
  - Wrede, Walther, "Kriegers ausfahrt in der archaisch-greichischen Kunst" Athenische Mitteilungen 41,., 1916; 2464.; pp.222-377 Taf.15-34 (Offprint, inscribed). (Box 46)
  - Wrede, "Marathon" Paulys Realenzyklopädie der Klassischen Altertumswissenschaft., 2465.; pp.1-3 (Offprint). (Box 46)
  - Wrede, Walther, "Mnesikles und der Nikepyrgos" Athenische Mitteilungen 57,., 1932; 2466.; pp.74-91 Beil. XIV-XV (Offprint, inscribed). (Box 46)
  - Wrede, Walther, "Phyle" Athenische Mitteilungen 39,., 1924; 2467.; pp.153-224, Taf.2-9 (Offprint, inscribed to [P]F). (Box 46)
  - Wrede, Walther, "Zur Caeretaner Busirisvase" Jahrbuch des Deutschen Archäologischen Instituts 1/2,., 1923/24; 2468.; col. [11]-14 (Offprint, inscribed to PF). (Box 46)
  - Wrede, Walther, review: Noack's Eleusis. Gnomon 10,., 1928; 2469.; pp.548-559 + plan (Offprint, inscribed). (Box 46)
  - Wülfing-v. Martitz, Peter, "IEPOS bei Homer und in der älteren griechischen Literatur" (fortsetzung) Glotta 39,., 1960; 2470.; pp.24-43 (Offprint, inscribed). (Box 46)
  - Wyller, Egil A., "Platons 'Ion': Versuch einer Interpretation" Symbolae Osloenses 34,., 1958; 2471.; pp.19-38 (Offprint, annotated). (Box 46)
  - Ziegler, Konrat, "Der Kreter Echemmas" Rheinisches Museumfür Philologie 87/1 s.d., 2472.; pp.74-80 (Offprint). (Box 46)
  - Zucker, Friedrich, [Review.] "Ture Kalén: Berliner Leihgabe griechischer Papyri... Uppsala, 1932...." Gnomon 11/7,., 1935; 2473.; pp.368-374 (Offprint, inscribed). (Box 46)
  - Zumin, Annamaria, "Epigrammi Sepolcrali Anonimi D'Eta" Classica ed Ellenistica" Rivista di Cultura classica e Medioevale 3/2,., 1961; 2474.; pp.186-223 (Offprint, inscribed). (Box 46)
  - Zuntz, Günther, "A Significant Book on the Language of the Septuagint" L'Antiquité Classique 223/1,., 1953; 2475.; pp.106-112 (Offprint). (Box 46)
  - Zuntz, Günther, "Euthalius = Euzoius?" Vigiliae Christianae 7/1,., 1953; 2476.; pp.16-22 (Offprint). (Box 46)
  - Zuntz, Günther, "Is the Heraclidae Mutilated?" s.l. s.a., 2477.; pp.46-52 (Offprint, inscribed). (Box 46)
  - Zuntz, Günther, "Melito - Syriac" Vigiliae Christianae 6/4,., 1952; 2478.; pp.193-201 (Offprint). (Box 46)
  - Zuntz, Günther, "Notes on Antoninus" ??., 2479.; pp.47-55 (Offprint, inscribed). (Box 46)
  - Zuntz, G., "ödipus und Gregorius: Tragödie und Legende" Antike und Abendland 4, s.a., 2480.; pp.191-203 (Offprint, corrected). (Box 46)
  - Zuntz, Günther, "On the Etymology of the Name Sappho" Museum Helveticum 8,., 1951; 2481.; pp.12-35 (Offprint, inscribed). (Box 46)
  - Zuntz, G., "On the First Verses of Euripides" Elektra" Rheinisches Museum 113,., 1970; 2482.; (Offprint) (box 1). (Box 46)
  - Zuntz, G., "On the Hymns in Corpus Hermeticum XIII" Hermes 83,., 1955; 2483.; pp.68-98 (Offprint, inscribed). (Box 46)
  - Zuntz, Günther, "On the Opening Sentence of Melito's Paschal Homily" Harvard Tlieological Review 36/4,., 1948; 2484.; pp.299-315 (Offprint). (Box 46)
  - Zuntz, Günther, "Réflexions sur l'Histoire du Texte Paulinien" La Revue Biblique 59,., 1952; 2485.; pp.5-22 (Offprint). (Box 46)
  - Zuntz, Günther, [Review:] "Wolf H. Friedrich, Euripides und Diphilos. Munich ......" ??., 1953; 2486.; pp.195-200 (Offprint). (Box 46)
  - Zuntz, Günther, "Zum Hymnus des Kleanthes" Rheinisches Museum für Philologie 94/4,., 1951; 2487.; pp.337-342 (Offprint). (Box 46)
  - Miscellaneous cuttings., 2488.; (14 items). (Box 46)
  - Unidentified fragments., 2489.; (7 sections; 9 covers). (Box 46)
  - Jaeger, Wezner, Paideia, 3 vols., annotated by Paul Friedländer., 2490. (Box 47)